Guide to the Harold A. Mooney Papers SC1183
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2016-119
  - Livestock in a Living Landscape
    - NCEAS, 2005 Jun (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - unlabeled, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Grantseeking, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Kellog foundation, 2005 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Archer Daniel Midlands (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Carton + Fire (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - ContiGroup Foundation, Companies (new york), 2005 Dec 9 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Unilever, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - USDA Agricultural Research Services OIRP, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Rockefeller Family Fund, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Koch data, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Janga + foil…, 2003 Oct (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Gummafin (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - German committee - SCOPE (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - ICSU (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - IGBP international geosphere- biosphere programme (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - FAO CIAP relative (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - outlook for indian poultry sector (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Bangkok, Thailand Structural changes in the livestock sector, 2004 Jan 27-29 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - LEAD, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Millennium Ecosystem Assessment
    - EPA/SAB Washington DC, 2004 Nov 2-3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Consulative Process towards an IMoSEB Bonn Germany, 2008 May 19-21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - correspondence, 2002 Nov-Dec (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Misc. work, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Combined WG Prague planning - crossout process (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - logistics, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - talk, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Synthesis - early, 2002 Sep 15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - D - budget drylands (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - D - drylands venue, 2003 Aug 12-15 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - D - CCD issues/memos, 2003 Aug 21 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - D - participants early, 2003 Aug 11-13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - D - visa/consular issues, 2003 Aug (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Visa support, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - user forum workshop, 2003 Jul 16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - logistics mar/ coastal (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - for transfer to main, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - APA/SAB committee Washington DC, 2004 Jun 13-14 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Drivers meeting, Frankfurt, Germany, 2002 Aug 20-25 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Drivers - Background (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - drivers of change in ecosystems, 2002 Dec 11-12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - FCS report components, materials, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - APA/SAB ecological systems and services Wasington DC, 2004 Feb 18 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Food cross cutting meeting, 2003 May 12-14 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Food x cut meeting travel, 2003 May 12-14 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - EPA/SAB ecological systems and services, 2004 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Atecame, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - M/C final report, 2003 Apr 7-11 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Biodiversity cross cut meeting Royal Society, London, 2002 Sep (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - MA followup Paris, 2007 Dec 11-12 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Committee Files
    - Geo-bon project overseas, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Reid and Mooney Ecosystem services - must people pay for these services?, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - ICSU Diversitas committee, 2007 Jan 1 - 2010 Dec 31 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - papers, 2003 Jul 16 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - AGEE special issue/encyclopedia, 2007 Mar (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Diversitas science plans (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bio 124, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Global change journals subscription info, 1993 Jul (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - UNEP linking human well-being ecosystem services and natural capital, 2006 Sep 6 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - SAGOFF - EPA, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - EPA (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - NAS BISO committee for biodiversity and ecosystem services A symposium, 2008 Aug 11 - 2009 Aug 31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Grade sheeh, 2005 Apr (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Bridging the rift dead sea project proposals and background (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - USDA review -- effects of climate change on agriculture, land resources, water resources and biodiversity CCSP synthesis and assessment (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - IFAA584 remote sensory, 2007 Jun (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - EPA/SAB valuing ecol systems and services San Francisco, 2004 Sep 13-15 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Mooney, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - NRC/BASC committee Analysis of global change assessments (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2018-098
  - TREE-MA-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Crosscut Issues/docs (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - MA Launch, Washington, 2003 Sep 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Current Work (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - MA Meeting, Prague, 2003 Oct 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SAFMA Pilot Assessment (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Diversitas (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ecosystem Function of Biodiversity, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Biodiversity (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Biodiversity (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Diversitas Nagoya, Japan, 2010 Mar 24 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - US Diversitas Phoenix, Arizona, 2008 Feb 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - US Diversitas Committee (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Biodiversity Research-Safeguarding the Future, 2008 May (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Diversitas Paris, 2003 Jan (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Diversitas US Committee, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Diversitas Paris, 2008 Mar (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Diversitas Open Science Conference, 2005 Nov 9 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Diversitas Paris, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fifth SC Diversitas Capetown, South Africa, 2007 Mar (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Climate Change-Global Risks, Challenges, Decisions, 2009 Mar (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NBER Conference-Built and Natural Environment Panel, 2009 Mar (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Darwin Symposium, Washington DC, 2009 Feb (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SC-Diversitas, Washington DC, 2009 Feb 8 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Geo Bon Organizational Meeting, Washington DC, 2009 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Biodiversity Forum, Washington DC, 2008 Dec 8 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Tel Aviv, Israel, 2008 Dec (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - IMOSEB-Malasia, 2008 Nov (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - IAI-Miami, Florida, 2008 Nov (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Planet 2050 Meeting, 2008 Oct 26 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - ICSU Members Forum/29th General Assembly, 2008 Oct (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Barcelona Declaration, 2008 Oct 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - SC-bioDiscovery Meeting, 2007 Sep (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - ALLP All-Cohorts Training, 2007 Sep (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Society of Environmental Journalists, 2007 Sep (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - IAI Scientific Advisory Committee, 2015 Aug (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ESA Annual Meeting, 2007 Aug (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - MA Follow-up (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 9th Kyoto University International Symposium, 2007 Jun 22 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Royal Society Workshop, 2007 Jun 12 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - NAS Annual Meeting, 2007 May 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ICSU MA Followup, 2007 Jan (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - GAO Workshop on Climate Change and Federal Lands, 2006 Nov 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2006 Science for Natural Symposium, 2006 Oct 31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ecosystem Services, 2006 Oct (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - EPA/CVPESS Committee, 2006 Oct 5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Adelaide (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 15th Australian Weeds Conference, 2006 Sep 24 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Italian Ecological Society, 2006 Sep 19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NRC/Global Change Assessments, 2006 Aug 15 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Botany Society of America, 2006 Aug 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bridging the Rift, 2006 Jul 23 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - EPA/AIS, Washington DC, 2006 Jun (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NRC/Global Change Assessments, 2006 May (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - EPA/SAB CVPESS, 2006 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - EPA/SAB CVPESS, 2006 Apr 18 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NRC/Global Change Assessments, 2006 Mar (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CIAP Workshop, 2006 Mar (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vegetation Management Workshop, 2006 Mar (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - RCBAS Advisory Committee, 2006 Mar (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NRC Committee Analysis of Global Change Assessments, 2006 Feb (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - IMOSEB-Paris, 2006 Feb 21 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Unlabeled (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - AAAS Meeting, 2006 Feb (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bridging the Rift, 2006 Jan (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - ESA Conference, 2006 Jan (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - EPA/SAB Workshop, 2005 Dec 13 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - MEA Workshop, 2005 Dec 2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - MIT Earth System Initiative Symposium, 2005 Nov 7 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Lane Environmental Lecture, 2005 Oct 25 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - ICSU General Assembly, 2005 Oct 18 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Creating Markets for Ecosystem Services, 2005 Oct (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Earth-Atmosphere Interactions Workshop, 2005 Sep 29 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Florida weed, 2003 Nov (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ecology Workshop, 2003 Sep 23 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ESA (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 10-19)